那帮悲哀女人读书会的人
The Sad Lady Book Club is reading
又在重读《五十度灰》了
Fifty Shades of Grey again.
书打动了所有人 "水"声经久不息
There's not a dry seat in the house.
如果这些女人都这么爱轻度性虐待
If those ladies are that into light torture,
来应征我们的工作就能被虐个爽啦
they should just apply for our jobs.
你们俩好有爱
Aww, you two are so adorable.
就像罗密欧与朱丽叶 但人家前途比你们光明
Like Romeo and Juliet, but without the bright future.
是啊...
Yeah...
我要让他离开餐厅
I want him out of the diner.
你在说什么傻话呢
What are you talking about?
所有在餐厅里工作的人
Anyone who works in this diner
就像是胖子坐小车
is like a fat guy in a smart car.
进去就出不来了
You can never get out.
这是真的
It's true.
我1962年时进来喝杯咖啡
I came in here in 1962 for a cup of coffee.
帮一个人找完钱后 就再也没离开这里了
Someone asked me to break a dollar, and I never left.
跟一个男的同住 同工 还同床
Look. Living, working, and sleeping with the same guy
绝不是一个好主意
is never a good idea.
不信你去问希拉里·克林顿
Just talk to Hillary Clinton.
我想我还是有办法让个洗碗工被炒吧
I guess I can get a dishwasher fired.
我还有钱时 让沃尔夫冈被自家餐厅炒掉过
When I was rich, I got Wolfgang Puck fired from Wolfgang Puck.
自作自受了吧 麦克斯
Get yours, Max!
打完就跑 拔屌无情
Hit it then quit it.
在我二三十岁时 这招受用无穷
That strategy served me well in my 20s and 30s.
晚上好啊 姑娘们
Evening, ladies.
七十多岁也能用哦
Also, my 70s.
上菜
Pick up.
随便吧
Or don't.
谁在乎啊
Who gives a crap?
有人在闹脾气 怎么啦 小格格
Well, someone's in a bad mood. What's wrong, Oleg?
你的男淫味身体喷雾停产了吗
Did they discontinue making Axe body spray?
这玩笑不许开
Don't even kid.
但不是啦 我不高兴是因为现在没爱做
No. I'm cranky because I'm not having sex right now.
对啊 我就觉得你说话时两手没在"下面"
Yeah. I thought it was weird seeing both your hands
有种不习惯的感觉
while you were talking.
苏菲的主意 波兰那边的老传统吧
Sophie's idea. It's some old Polish ritual.
新郎跟新娘婚前30天要保持"贞洁"
The bride and groom remain chaste for 30 days before the wedding.
看来婚礼上需要的"蓝色的东西"
Apparently, the "something blue" at the wedding
是我憋得发青的蛋蛋
has got to be my balls.
所以你在练习禁欲
So, you're practicing celibacy.
我在尝试啊 可是到处都有女人
I'm trying, but there are women everywhere.
感觉自己像走进逼店里的公牛
I feel like a bull in a vagina shop.
听我说 听我说
Hear ye, hear ye!
我要宣布我们餐厅的一项重大进步
I'm unveiling a major improvement to the diner!
我们会想念你的 阿憨
Well, we'll miss you, Han.
像得美 麦克斯 我就像瑞安·西克雷斯特
Nice try, Max, but like Ryan Seacrest,
我会永远都在这里
I'll be here forever.
现在请你们做你们推特上还没做的事
Now, will you all please do what you have yet to do on Twitter
跟[粉]我走
and follow me?
你也来 厄尔
You too, Earl.
靠 你这事最好够重要
Hell, this better be good.
我走的每一步都可能是最后一步呢
Every step I take could be my last.
现在
And now...
废物少说
Without further a-douche...
准备好要被吓炸了吗
Ready to have your minds blown?
憋到现在 我啥都准备要炸了
At this point, I'm ready to have anything blown.
看啊
Ta-da!
这是我这辈子收过最烂的礼物了
That is the worst gift I ever received
而且我儿子去年还送过我棺材呢
and last year, my son bought me a coffin.
那太好了 因为压根就不是送你的
This works our great then, because it's not for you.
是要送纳西
It's for Nash.
那太好了
Oh, well, that's real nice.
因为麦克斯家的浴室莲蓬头坏了
Because the shower at Max's place doesn't work at all.
这东西肯定赞
You better believe it's nice.
这可是喷喷5000型
That's the Spritzy 5000.
《每周洗碗工杂志》给了他四碗级评价呢
Dishwasher Weekly gave it four out of four Dishies.
你知道咱们店里的烤箱也是坏的吧
You know our oven doesn't work, right?
老板娘
Hey, boss lady,
如果我们工作认真 也会有礼物吗
if we work hard, do we get a gift?
如果有你工作认真的那天
If you work hard, I'll die childless
我会膝下无子 惊讶地张嘴死去
with my mouth frozen open in shock.
我就说得这么狠 咋地
Yeah, I went there!
纳西工作认真 所以只让他用我的小水管
Nash works hard, so only he may handle my beautiful hose!
如果他在用阿憨的"小水管"
Well, if he's handling Han's hose,
那他永远也不会被炒掉了
he's never getting fired.
过来吧 纳西
Okay. Step up here, Nash.
我让你看看这玩意[小狗]可以干嘛
I'll show you what this puppy can do.
目前这只小狗碰不到水管啊
So far the puppy can't reach the hose.
帮个忙
A little help.
帅哥抱着婴儿时最有爱了
Aww, there's nothing cuter than a hot guy holding a baby.
你就抓住那管子 挤压它 直到它喷出来
Now just grab that thing and squeeze it till it sprays.
我要求在我结婚前冻结以下字眼
Move to call a moratorium on the words "grab," "squeeze,"
"抓住 挤压 喷出"
and "sprays" till the wedding.
我去 太性感了吧
Damn! That's hot.
可惜我身上没有零钱塞进他的裤子里[舞男]
And me without any singles to stuff down his pants.
我去男厕里弄干吧
Well, I better go dry off in the men's room.
别占着隔间太久
Don't be too long in that stall.
我晚点休息时跟黄油包装上的印第安姑娘
I've got a date with the Land O'Lakes butter package lady
有场"约会"
on my next break.
抱歉 女士们 我全身湿了
Pardon me, ladies. I'm all wet.
麦克斯 你看到我看到的事了吗
Max? Are you seeing what I'm seeing?
老女人把他当成
Those ladies looking at him
自助餐店里的"老人特餐"吗
like he's a senior special at Sizzler's?
或许我们没办法让纳西被炒掉
We might not be able to get Nash fired,
但我们能让他变成时尚模特被别人录用啊
but we can get him hired as a fashion model.
你看她们的表情
Look at their faces.
他可以当名牌的下一个内裤模特啊
He could be the future bulge of Calvin Klein.
现在还开始说起什么未来啦
Now you're talking about the future?
为什么你就不能接受我们被困在
Why can't you just accept that we are stuck
这个烂到爆的现实[礼物]这件事呢
with a really crappy present?
不许再说喷喷5000的坏话
Quit trash-talking the Spritzy 5000!
下午好 欢迎来到嗨翻天
Good afternoon. Welcome to The High.
马上会有人给你倒水
I'll have somebody get you some water.
不是我 因为我早已不干这种活了
Not me, 'cause I'm past that.
在这家店时不是
You know, here.
我刚才好像又帮我们老板
I think I just sat another one of those
带她的拉拉相亲对象就座了
lesbian blind-dates for our boss.
这年头当老鸨不容易啊
It's hard out there for a pimp.
不然你觉得我为啥退出这行
Why do you think I got out of pimping?
就因为这个 再加上有人拿啤酒瓶爆了我头
That and someone broke a beer bottle over my head.
你给纳西找到模特工作了吗
So, did you get Nash a modeling job yet?
我在弄呢
I'm working on it.
又不是我打给超模节目主持人就能摆平
It's not like I can just call Tyra Banks.
至少我打过去时 她底下的人是这么说的
Well, that's what her people said when I called.
电话心理辅导有点超时了
Ugh, phone therapy ran long.
显然女性访谈节目主持人的离开
Apparently I have more issues
对我内心造成的伤害比想象中严重
than I realized about Rosie leaving The View.
我的相亲对象到了吗
Are my dates here yet?
别告诉我是她 她 或她
Please don't tell me it's her, her, or her.
就是她 她 和她
It's her, her, and her.
快把她们弄走
Lose them.
我怎么把她们弄走啊
How am I supposed to get rid of them?
就说跟其他人想拉拉离开时一样的话啊
Just say what anyone says when they want a lesbian to leave,
"外面有台斯巴鲁要被开罚单了"
"There's a Subaru outside that's about to get a ticket."
如果你十年前告诉我
If you had you told me, ten years ago,
我以后会上一个相亲网叫"千里拉拉一线牵"
I'd be on a dating site called "Lez Meet Up,"
我会告诉我当年嫁的那位牧师
I would've told the youth pastor I was married to,
"你真是疯了"
"You've lost your mind."
模特公司刚发给我
Oh, I just got some interest
表示他们对纳西有兴趣
from the Del Monico Modeling Agency.
要如果要面试 需要先传照片
But for the interview, he needs photos.
不只是你手机上他的屁股照那种
And not just the pictures of his butt on your phone.
好吧 这事交给你了
Fine, you handle it.
我对当模特的唯一认识是几年前
The only thing I know about modeling is
我曾是问诊网站上"带状疱疹"的封面
a couple of years ago, I was the face of shingles on WebMD.
姑娘们 你们找我帮你们拍照的时间点太棒
Girls, perfect timing to ask me to do this photo shoot.
联调局上周刚把我的相机还我
The FBI just gave me my camera back last week.
所以你的相机能拿回来
Oh, so you get your camera back,
可我还得继续等我那些
but I'm still waiting on that kilo of coke
花了数小时才塞进我菊花里的一公斤白粉吗
that I spent hours carefully filling my butt with?
让我修改一下设定
Let me just change the settings.
这相机本来是用来拍240多公尺外的照片
This camera is used to taking pictures from 800 feet away.
请把你偷拍我们的照片还来 奥列格
And we want those pictures back, Oleg!
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
请叫我"尖峰时段车潮姐"
Just call me "rush hour traffic"
因为我好饥渴[狂按喇叭]
'cause I sure am horny.
卡洛琳 我不知道你是怎么憋过一年 加一年
Oh, Caroline, I do not know how you go years, and years,
加一年 加一年 加一年 再加一年
and years, and years, and years, and years
无性生活日子
without doing the nasty.
只有一年加一年好吗
It's only been years and years.
-少来 -再加一年
- Come on. - And years.
我好想吃个牛腩三明治
Well, I could go for a brisket sandwich.
我们关门了 苏菲
We're closed, Sophie.
我知道 我包包里有
I know. I got one in my purse.
为什么你们要在这肮脏的洗碗房里拍照呢
And why are you doing the photo shoot in this skanky dishroom?
因为我们要走"性感洗碗工"的路线
Because we're going with the "hot dishwasher" angle.
经纪公司说每个模特都需要个特色
The agency said every model needs a hook.
比如超模辛迪·克劳馥有颗媒婆痣
Yeah, like how Cindy Crawford has a beauty mark
模特安娜·妮可·史密斯的招牌就是死了
and Anna Nicole Smith is dead.
对啊 我在波兰就有个姐妹有特色[钩子]
Yeah, yeah. My sister is a model in Poland and she has a hook.
装在她的左手上
It's her left hand, yeah.
还很适合卖中东肉串
It's is also great for kabobs.
快出来啊 纳西
Come on, Nash!
走路给我来点自信[爱尔兰肥皂]
Put a little Irish Spring in your step.
我有点紧张
I'm a little nervous.
除了这次 我唯一拍过照就是在学校时
The only other time I had my picture taken was at school.
学校牧师说他的点名册上需要我的裸身照
The priest said he needed a shirtless one for the roll call.
他是上的什么学校啊
Where did he go to school,
圣母玛利亚之抓恋童癖学院吗
Our Lady of To Catch a Predator?
妈呀 看了就好想扑倒啊
Wow. You sure look hot.
注意点 苏菲
Careful, Sophie.
这块牛腩是我的
That's my brisket.
我又不是在说这块爱尔兰烂牛腩
I'm not talking about Daniel Day-Loser here.
我是在说奥列格
I'm talking about Oleg.
你汗流浃背就像一根在太阳底下
You are sweating like an old knockwurst
被晒到臭掉的德国大香肠
that has been left out in the sun.
那股味儿 挡都挡不住
It's really breathtaking.
好了 纳西 站到水管这里来
Okay, Nash, stand over here near the hose
给我一副帅气脸 死人眼的表情
and give me hot face, dead eyes.
就像我把日间跟夜间感冒糖浆混着喝时那样
You know, like me when I mix NyQuil and DayQuil.
我称那为"下午爽一杯"
I call it AfternoonQuil.
好 我准备拍[射]了
Okay. Now I'm gonna start shooting.
射把 宝贝 射吧
Yeah. Shoot, baby! Shoot!
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
他好僵"硬" 但硬错地方了
Well, he's stiff, but not in the good way.
简直不忍直视
Ugh, this is painful.
就像是没有巨星才华的苏珊大妈
He's like Susan Boyle without the star quality.
我们需要给他加点之前的"料"
We need a little of what he had the other day.
你之后会感谢我
You'll thank me for this later.
没错 纳西 没错
Yes, Nash, yes!
把衣服撕掉
Tear your shirt!
-好耶 赞啊 -好耶 赞啊
- Yeah, yeah. - Oh, yeah, yeah.
停下
Stop!
这里他妈的是在干嘛
What the hell is happening in here?
我可没给过任何人把餐厅当摄影棚的权力
I didn't give anyone permission to use my diner for a photo shoot.
冷静点
Calm down.
我们在想办法帮他弄到份模特工作
We are trying to get him a modeling job.
他有一份工作了 我的头号员工
He has a job! He's my number one worker.
就像你妈妈生出你时 医生对她说的
Like the doctor said to your mother when you were born,
节哀
tough break.
你们俩只乌鸦就是得把我的东西都抢光
You two crows don't let me have anything!
好了 纳西 模特的面试里有部分是要看
Okay, Nash, part of the model audish is to see
你在广告 电影 以及没人看的一些东西里
how you'd be as a performer in commercials, and movies,
会有怎么样的表现
and other things people don't watch anymore.
首先 不用想也知道
Now, obviously, right out of the gate,
你虽然比不上美国家庭人寿广告上的鸭子
you're not gonna be as good as that duck who says "Aflac,"
但你再差也得是演员本·阿弗莱克那档次吧
but you've got to be at least as good as Ben Affleck.
这我能帮忙 我也曾经有过辉煌的演艺生涯
I can help. For a time, I had a rich acting career.
我一开始就在音乐剧《安妮》出演主角
It started with a starring role in Annie,
出演黑人民权运动之母
in an ill-advised high school production
最后还被全国有色人种协进会调查了呢
that led to an investigation by the NAACP.
这是早餐麦片的广告呢
Ooh, this is a commercial for breakfast cereal!
每个演员的"梦想"啊
Ah! Every actor's dream!
纳西 你来念念
Hey, Nash, read this.
学学詹姆斯·迪恩
Think James Dean.
但是还活着 而且正吃着可可泡芙麦片
But alive and eating Cocoa Puffs.
"抠抠泡胡素你每天
"Cocoa Puffs are a delicious part
好出的银养早餐的必备品"
of any well-balanced breakfast."
我在想该怎么说才比较好听...
I'm trying to find a nice way to say--
你太烂了吧 兄弟
You suck, bro.
你能懂吧
You--you get it.
那种能在非吃巧克力时段
You know the thrill of eating chocolate
却能吃到巧克力的兴奋感吧
at a traditionally non-chocolatey time of day.
朝这个方向再琢磨下
Let's tap into that.
好了 从头来过
Okay. Take it from the top.
但这一次疯狂[杜鹃]一点
And this time, go cuckoo.
我为可可泡芙狂[广告词]
Go cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs.
"抠抠泡胡素你每天..."
"Cocoa Puffs are a delicious--"
停
Stop.
别这么敷衍好吗 这又不是提子麦片
Don't phone this in. It's not Raisin Bran.
"泡抠抠胡素你每天..."
"Pocoa Cuffs are a delicious--"
"泡抠抠胡"
"Pocoa Cuffs"?
泡抠抠胡
Pocoa Cuffs?
我跟这种业余小白待不下去了 卡洛琳
I just can't with these rank amateurs, Caroline.
麦克斯 冷静
Max, calm down.
这是麦片广告的一次假试镜
It's a fake tryout for a cereal commercial,
又不是《舞蹈妈妈》
not Dance Moms.
人家紧张嘛 我不是演员的料
I'm nervous. I'm not an actor.
没错 你的确不是
Uh, no, you are not.
把台词给我
Give me that.
记住了
Got it.
营养均衡的早餐 可可泡芙添美味
Cocoa Puffs are a delicious part of any well-balanced breakfast!
有益健康父母爱
They're good for you, which parents love,
味道香甜我更爱
and they taste like candy, which I love!
情难自禁喊一句 我为可可泡芙狂
I can't help it! I'm cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs!
疯啦
Cuckoo!
我要落泪了 不光是因为家里长了黑霉
I'm tearing up, and it's not just the black mold in here.
麦克斯 你刚才可能把表演标准拉得太高了
Max, I think you may have just set the acting bar too high.
我没试过将一个酒吧变得太嗨[将标准拉高]
I've never set a bar too high before.
我试过放火烧酒吧 也试过嗨着出酒吧
I've set a bar on fire and I've left a bar too high.
姑娘们
Oh, hey, girls.
你们介意我在楼下跟你们待一会儿吗
Oh, do you mind if I hang down here with you for a while?
奥列格在楼上
Oleg is up there,
他企图通过打扫公寓来色诱我
he's trying to seduce me by cleaning the apartment.
而且楼上真是...太"肮脏"了
And it's, oh, oh, so dirty.
他在用真空吸尘器 这意味着他也"真空"
Oh, oh, he's vacuuming now, which means he's naked.
天啊 我和我的波兰价值观要撑不住了
Oh, me and my Polish values.
波兰价值
Polish Values?
我最喜欢的一家布鲁克林一元店也叫这个
That's the name of my favorite dollar store in Brooklyn.
他在深层清洁毛地毯
Oh, he's deep-cleaning the shag.
老天 来人啊
Oh, my God. Somebody,
快浇熄我的欲火
do something to make me not want sex.
好的 纳西 走台步给我们看
All right, Nash, why don't you show us your runway walk?
走完了
That was it.
好吧 我以为你是过去拿支笔的
Oh, I thought you were going to pick up a pen.
太好了 谢谢
Thanks, perfect.
现在我的欲火完全熄灭了
Now I'm completely turned off.
看这傻帽从那头走过来 真让人性致全无
Watching that potato walk across the room really did the trick.
纳西 集中注意力
Nash, concentrate.
看我的示范
Follow my lead.
右扭 左扭 右扭 左扭
Bam. Pow. Bam. Pow.
前一步右点脚 转身左前点脚
And step and bam, and step and pow,
退一步左后点脚
and step and bam!
这更好
Oh, even better!
看完你走台步 我的私密处都可以拍
I mean, after that, they could film the sequel
《冰雪奇缘》的续集了
to Frozen on my lady parts.
深有同感
Yeah, me too.
但只是因为我"随它去"下面
But just 'cause I "Let it go" down there.
他现在用外接吸头了[电动棒外接头]
Oh, now he's using the wand attachment.
天啊 他要"深入"地吸抱枕了
Oh, and he's getting real deep between the cushions.
去他妈的价值观
Oh, my God, just screw it.
老娘憋不到婚礼了
I'm never gonna make it to the wedding!
科臣斯基奶奶 请原谅
Oh, Grandma Kuchenski, please forgive me
我即将要干的事
for what I'm about to do.
我...
I--
算了 你自己也不是贞洁圣女
Well, you were no White Lily yourself!
他在积极练习左扭右扭
He's bamming and powing up a storm.
日后他出名了 希望他会记得我们
When he's famous, I hope he remembers us.
切 我就做了一些他"日后"绝不会忘记的事
Pfft. I like to think I did some things he will never forget.
如何
How's that?
很棒 看来你会走路
Great, you can walk.
如果你也识字 那我可以开瓶果汁庆祝下
If you can read too, I'll treat myself to a Snapple.
我们来试念台词吧
Let's get to the copy.
其实我们有备而来
Actually, we came prepared.
纳西排练过可可泡芙的广告
Nash rehearsed the Cocoa Puffs commercial.
我觉得一定能打动你
I think you'll be quite moved.
是吗
Oh yeah,
我们今天要念点不一样的
well, we'll be reading something a little different today.
别慌 他们总是这样
Don't panic. They do this all the time.
就是为了确保你的可塑性强
They want to make sure you're flexible.
是啊 加油 纳西
Yeah. Go ahead, Nash.
不管是什么麦片 都要表现出很好吃的样子
Whatever cereal it is, act like it's delicious.
除了卜卜米 淡而无味
Unless it's Rice Krispies. A-boring!
好了 开始吧
Okay, here goes.
"嘴上说不要 身子却很诚实嘛
"You know you like it.
弯下身子 贱婢"
Bend over, bitch."
是不是少了一页
Uh, are we missing a page?
现在的麦片广告跟我小时候的差好多哦
Cereals have changed since I was a kid.
我应该念出我发现
Should I read the part where I notice
老师没有穿内裤的那一段吗
the teacher's not wearing any panties?
我的老天 这是黄片啊
Oh, my God. This is porn!
怪不得坐外面的人看起来都这么变态
No wonder all those people out there were freaks.
怪不得我大部分都认识
No wonder I recognized so many of them.
别装得这么惊讶
Don't act so surprised.
谁不知道可可泡芙是黄片的暗号啊
Everyone knows Cocoa Puffs is code for porn.
还有你寄过来的照片一看就是
Also, you sent us some pictures taken by someone
出自某位色情大师之手
very experienced in erotica.
我们不能让他入这行
We can't let him do this.
我有部电影明天就开始拍摄
I have a movie that starts shooting tomorrow
片酬是一千块一天哦
that pays $1,000 a day.
能吗
Can we?
或许不能吧
Maybe we can't.
是《阿干屁传》的主角哦
It's the lead in Sorest Rump.
或许能
Maybe we can.
我们俩需要私聊一下 德洛莉丝
I think we need a little sidebar, Delores.
我该跟你一起去吗
Should I come with you?
不用 没事的
No, we're good.
我有几个问题要问演员
I have a couple of questions for the actor.
你会游泳吗 你割包皮了吗
Can you swim, and are you circumcised?
麦克斯 这太离谱了
Max, this has gone too far.
我知道 我曾经也以为你只是
I know, I was expecting you to just crash with me
借宿几天就搬走呢
for a couple of days and get your own place.
我们真的要让纳西去拍黄片吗
Are we really gonna let Nash do porn
就为了不让他留在餐厅工作
just so he doesn't work at the diner?
女士们 讨论出结果了吗
Hey, ladies, what's it gonna be?
另一位演员还等着我面试呢
I got other talent to see.
那人叫贾湿丁·逼勃
I got a guy named Lustin Beaver
从费城大老远坐火车过来的
taking the Amtrak in from Philly.
麦克斯 如果你真的想让我当黄片演员
Max, if you're really keen on me being a porn actor,
我愿意
I'll do it.
她说明天开始拍摄
She says, tomorrow, they start filming
《波大屁湿大饭店》
The Grand Booty Fest Hotel.
而且因为我的口音加分又加钱
And, they'll pay me more for my accent.
对了 "出租男同"是什么意思啊
Also, what does "Gay for pay" mean?
意思是我们该走了
Ugh, I guess it means we got to go.
瞧瞧他 麦克斯
Look at him, Max.
又一个被演艺圈吸干吐出的帅小伙
A cute guy, eaten up and spat out by show business
就像他之前千千万万个鲍德温兄弟
like so many Baldwin brothers before him.
纳西才不在乎当不当模特
Nash doesn't care about modeling.
他才21岁 他什么都不在乎
He's 21. He doesn't care about anything.
他最关心的问题是能不能玩Xbox
His biggest concern is playing with the XBox.
指的是我下面 还有受欢迎的电子游戏机
Mine and, also, the popular video game system.
他在乎你
He cares about you.
他为了你都愿意当"出租男同"了
He was willing to do "gay for pay."
我刚是听见纳西要当"出租男同"吗
Did I hear Nash is going "Gay for pay"?
我口袋里可是有4块钱租金迫切想租下他
'Cause I've got $4 burning a hole in my pocket.
有客人来了
Oh, a customer.
你好 欢迎来到嗨翻天 来吃甜点吗
Hi, welcome to The High. Here for dessert?
谢了 我16岁生日派对候后我就没吃过蛋糕
Oh, thanks but I haven't had cake since my Sweet 16,
即便当时 我还强迫自己把蛋糕吐出来了
and even then, I made myself throw it up.
我约了人在这里见面 而我的手机快没电了
I'm meeting someone here and my phone's about to die.
如果它没电了 那我也没命了
And if it dies, I will too.
你有电源插座吗[发泄途径]
Do you have an outlet?
洗澡的时候大叫对我很管用
Screaming in the shower really works for me.
直接对着水嚷嚷
Like, right into the water.
太可爱了 但我真的需要一个手机充电插座
Super cute. But I do need a phone outlet.
我帮你"插" 亲爱的
I'll plug you in, honey,
我也会处理好你的手机 放心
and I'll take care of your phone, too.
姑娘们 这位是玛丽
Girls, meet Marie.
你们好 说真的 就剩10%的电了
Hi. Seriously, down to 10%.
你们俩是在"千里拉拉一线牵"上认识的吗
Oh, did you two meet on "Lez Meet Up"?
不 亲爱的 我从未用过那玩意
No, honey, I've never been on "Lez Meet Up."
你说的是我吧 卡洛琳
Oh, you're thinking of me, Caroline.
你也知道我有多喜欢女人屁股
You know how much I love lady tail.
这地方太棒了
This place is amazing.
是不是超级棒呀
Isn't it amazing?
我让设计师返工了九次
I had the decorator redo it nine times.
墙上每一个细节都能感受到他的怒火
You can feel his anger in the walls.
激情四射
It's electric.
我们才激情四射 这位神来之笔是谁
We're electric. Who is this miracle?
他是纳西 是我一手发掘了他
That's Nash. I found him in the Bowery
在包厘街的一堆焚烧垃圾旁
next to a pile of burning trash.
去打个招呼吧
Go say hi.
近距离的他更奶油可口哟
He's even creamier and more delicious up close.
你在吃东西啊 太有朋克范了
You're eating? That is so punk rock.
快跟我说说你自己
Tell me everything right now.
我是一名洗碗工
Uh, well, I'm a dishwasher.
我来自爱尔兰
I'm from Ireland.
我想成为一名模特
Oh, I was trying to become a model
但一小时前差点去拍黄片
and I almost did porn an hour ago.
这是我这辈子听过最棒的故事
That is the best story I ever heard.
站起来再讲一遍
Tell it to me again standing up.
但这次 不要说话
But this time, don't talk.
有颜值有翘臀 有模特潜质
I see face, I see ass, I see model.
你有经纪人吗
Do you have a manager?
应该是卡洛琳 那边的金发妹
I guess that'd be Caroline, the blonde one over there.
金发妹 快过来跟我介绍下你的艺人
Blonde one, come over here and talk to me about your client.
我爱上他了 他太完美了
I am in love. He's perfection.
玛丽·普劳厄 高级营销副总裁
Marie Prower, Senior VP of Marketing.
太好了 什么公司
Sweet, what company?
盖尔斯[猜]
Guess.
汤米·希尔费格
Um, Tommy Hilfinger.
我在盖尔斯公司工作 亲爱的
I work for Guess, darling.
别说话了 听我说
No more words. Listen.
他棒呆了
He's amazing.
我想现在就把他放上推特 但我的手机没电了
I would tweet about him right now, but my phone is dead.
所以周一把他带来我的办公室
So bring him into my office on Monday.
你听见啦 卡洛琳
You heard her, Caroline.
明天带他去她的办公室
Bring him into her office tomorrow.
她超爱我
She's obsessed with me.
麦克斯 我说对了 他是做模特的料
Max, I was right. He is a model.
给我个辣妹老婆再给我个更辣的妞搞出轨
Get me a hot wife and a hotter woman to cheat on her with,
这是我这样的大牌经纪的标配
'cause I'm a big-time talent manager.
恭喜你啦 伙计
Congratulations, dude.
如果面试成功了
Well, I guess if this works out,
我就得辞掉餐厅的工作了
I'm gonna have to quit my job at the diner.
你会生我的气吗
Will you be mad at me?
我会非常难过
I'll be really sad.
我会非常想你 知道吗
I'm gonna miss you a lot, you know?
不能天天从早到晚看见你
Not seeing you 24/7.
但同时我也会恨自己
But I would hate myself
如果我不让你去追求你的梦想
if I didn't let you follow your dreams.
即使那意味着
Even if it means
你要从公寓搬走
you moving out of the apartment, too.
走吧
Now go.
我又要落泪了
Here comes that tear again.
我都哽咽了
I'm all choked up.
麦克斯 你演黑人民权之母一定很棒
Max, you would have made a great Rosa Parks.
前提是你是黑人的话
If you had been Black.
协会的人当初就是在坚持这个吧
Which, I guess, is what they insist on.
但你终于让他搬走了
But you got him to move out.
你演技太好了
You are good.
是啊 他是帅气又可爱
Yeah, well, I mean, he's cute,
可惜姐姐对他的"小泡芙"没有那么疯狂
but I'm not all that cuckoo for his Cocoa Puffs.